菲比，可以麻烦接个电话吗？
-Phoebe,could you get that,please?
为什么？就因为你懒得抬你的屁股？
-Why?Just because you're too lazy to get up off your tushy?
不是，只是因为在全世界 我只想跟你说话
No,it's just that all the people in the world I would want to talk to are right here.
真好骗
Sucker.
喂？乔伊
Hello?Hey,Joey!
菲比，帮我个忙好吗？
-Hey,Phoebe.I need a favor.
我忘记提款卡的密码 你可以帮我去找吗？
I forgot the PlN to my ATM card. Can you get it for me?
好啊，在哪里？
Sure. Where is it?
我刻在提款机的角落那里
I scratched it on the ATM machine on the corner.
原来5639是你的密码
So you're 5-6-3-9?
没错，菲比，谢了
That's it! Thanks.
你要跟钱德说话吗？
-Wanna talk to Chandler?
是乔伊吗？让我跟他说
-Is that Joey？Let me talk to him.
不要！他不相信我的电影
No，He didn't believe in my movie...
他大错特错 这次的电影是真的！…
...which is a big mistake,because it is real. Real.
崔比亚尼
Tribbiani,
快回去工作，休息时间结束了
get back to work. Break time's over.
刚才那个是谁？
-Who was that?
我的替身 他有点太没大没小了
-My stunt double. Yeah.He's getting a little too familiar for my tastes.
我这星期来都试着跟他道歉 若他不让我在电话上说
I've tried to apologize.If I can't do it on the phone,
我就直接杀过去当面说
I'll go and do it in person.
菲比，我听到了，请他听电话
I heard that. Can you put him on?
好
Yes
你别过来
Don't come out here.
不行…我百分之百支持你 我要当面证明给你看
I support you 100% and I wanna prove that to you in person.
收到，我原谅你，你别过来
I got that. I forgive you. Don't come out here.
原谅我？ 你一星期都不接我电话
You haven't taken my calls for a week.
钱德，我早都不介意了 咱们是一辈子的朋友
I'm totally over it. Friends forever.
你别过来
Don't come out here.
可以跟我们照张相吗？
Would you mind doing a picture with us?
那是什么？
-What was that?
“今夜娱乐”节目
-Entertainment Tonight.
好了，很高兴跟你说话 你别过来
Good talking to you and don't come out here.
本集播出：“拉斯维加斯之行”
The One in Vegas
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
莫妮卡，抱歉我迟到了
Monica? I'm sorry I'm late.
莫妮卡？
Monica？
菲比？
Phoebe？
菲比，真对不起
Phoebe I'm so sorry.
你到很久了吗？
Have you been here long?
没关系啦
That's okay.
你怎么拖了那么久？
What the hell took you so long?
好，不许你跟钱德说
You can't tell Chandler.
我遇见了理查
I ran into Richard.
哪个理查？ 那个理查
-Which Richard? -The Richard.
理查西蒙斯？天啊 （健身教练）
Richard Simmons? Oh,my God!
不是啦，是我前男友理查 个子高高，有胡子那个
No,my ex-boyfriend Richard. You know,the tall guy,mustache.
好吧，这就说得过去了
Okay,that actually makes more sense.
情况如何？
How was it?
好极了，我们先是闲聊 后来一起吃了个午饭
It was really nice. We talked and I had lunch with him.
怪了，我有梦到你跟理查吃饭
That's weird. I dreamed you had lunch with Richard.
真的？ 不过是跟理查西蒙斯啦
-Really? -Again,Richard Simmons.
你继续说
Go on.
奇怪的是虽然他很棒也很帅
The strange part was he was really nice and he looks great,...
但是我对他完全没感觉了
...but I didn't feel anything.
那为什么不能跟钱德说？
So why can't we tell Chandler?
因为他听了一定会发神经
Because it would totally freak him out
明天就是我们的纪念日 我不想搞砸
and tomorrow's our anniversary. I don't wanna spoil it.
不敢相信你们交往一年了
I can't believe you guys have lasted a whole year!
我欠瑞秋20美元
Wow,I owe Rachel 20 bucks.
什么？
What？
是个完全不相干的打赌
On a totally different bet.
一周年纪念日快到了
-It's almost our anniversary!
我知道
-I know.
你相信吗？一年前的今天 我还只是烦人的朋友钱德
One year ago today,I was just your annoying friend Chandler.
现在你是我烦人的朋友钱德
Now you're just my annoying friend Chandler.
我帮你买了礼物
I got you a gift.
纪念日明天才到
-It's not till tomorrow.
我知道，但你今天就要开礼物
-I know,but you have to open it today.
好吧
Okay
让我来
Okay! There you go!
两张去拉斯维加斯的机票
It's two tickets to Vegas!
这周末的来回机票
Yeah! For this weekend!
一定很完美，不但能去看乔伊 还能在飞机上开始过纪念日
It'll be perfect.You'll see Joey,plus,we'll start our celebration on the plane.
就叫做“飞机纪念日”吧
We can call it our "Plane-aversary."
一定要这样叫？
Do we have to?
不用啦
No
是很棒 但乔伊说了不要我们过去
This is great,but Joey didn't want any of us there.
他只是怕麻烦我们而已
He doesn't want us to go to any trouble.
到时我们突然出现 他一定很兴奋的
He'll be excited when we surprise him.
而且我们自己还有拉斯维加斯纪念日
Plus,we get to have our own "Anna-Vegas-ry"!
内华达纪念日！
"Anna-vada-versary!"
我想我们应该和别人交往试试
I think we should see other people.
我们可以去吧？ 是的
We can go,right?  Yes
这是个好主意
Great idea.
好耶，我也要去
I'm gonna go too!
菲比，这是我俩的纪念日
Phoebe,it's kind of our anniversary.
少来，休想像伦敦那次 把我抛下
Please，You won't ditch me like you did with London.
抛下？菲比， 当时你怀了三胞胎耶
Ditch you? You were pregnant
很棒的借口，我非去不可
Great story. I'm going.
注意，这周末大家一起去拉斯维加斯 给乔伊一个惊喜
Listen,this weekend we're all gonna go to Las Vegas to surprise Joey!
包括我！
Including me!
你们要去吗？
Do you wanna go?
我应该可以请个几天假
I can take a couple days off work.
你当然可以请几天假 因为这趟我也要去！
Of course you can take a couple days off,because this trip includes me!
等等，差点忘了 我明天有个报告，不能缺席
I've got a presentation tomorrow. I can't miss that.
我也买了梵高画展的票 我盼了一年才盼到
I've got tickets to the Van Gogh exhibit. I waited a year for this.
艺术爱好者
Art lover.
你说什么？
What'd you say?
我说艺术爱好者
I said,art lover.
那是用来侮辱人的吗？
-Was that supposed to be an insult?
不知道，我很累了
-I don't know,I'm very tired.
瑞秋，不如你我周六再飞去？
-Rach,maybe we can fly out Saturday?
听起来很可行 好，那我打电话去订票
-Sounds great.I'll call the airlines.
其实想起来很不赖 我可以独自在公寓过一晚
That'll be nice to have the apartment to myself.
对，你可以脱光到处走
To walk around naked.
不是，我可以自己一个人 享受独处的时光
No,so I can be by myself. Have a little alone time.
脱光的独处时光
Naked alone time.
菲比，我一个人独处 并不表示我就想脱光到处走
Just because I'm alone doesn't mean I wanna walk around naked.
你自己一个人住 你也不会脱光到处走啊
You live alone,you don't walk around naked.
你以为我为何总是很长时间才给你开门？
Why does it takes me so long to answer the door?
这趟旅程到现在为止 比起伦敦那趟好还是坏？
So far,is this trip to Las Vegas better or worse than the trip to London?
菲比，到现在为止都差不多
So far,it's pretty much the same,Phoebe.
好，那我给你们糖果之后呢？
What about after I give you these candies?
对，我想好一点了
I guess it's a little better now.
好，拉斯维加斯1分，伦敦0分
Las Vegas,1. London,0.
我马上回来
I'll be back.
飞机纪念日快乐
Happy Plane-aversary.
我爱你
I love you.
礼物能趁现在给你吗？
-Can I give you your present now?
好啊
-Okay!
我不会犯这种错误吧？
Oh,don't tell me I did this.
我最爱你假装没带礼物了
I love "l forgot the present" fake-out!
那如果我是真的没带礼物 请你多多包涵呢？
How about "I did forget the present,forgive me" not fake-out?
没关系啦，别放在心上 等回去再给我就行了
You can give it to me when we get back.
纪念日发生这种事 真是再扫兴不过了
This is the worst thing that could happen.
很好，你最后还是决定 要跟钱德说理查的事了
You decided to tell him about the Richard thing.
什么理查的事？
What "Richard thing"?
糟糕
Oh,no.
什么理查的事？
What "Richard thing"?
用西蒙斯混过去
Simmons. Go with Simmons.
好吧，我昨天遇到了理查
I ran into Richard yesterday.
他问我要不要一起吃饭 我答应了
He asked me if I wanted to go for a bite and I did.
我没跟你说是因为
I didn't tell you because ...
我知道你会生气 而我不想毁了周年纪念日
...you'd get mad and I didn't wanna spoil our anniversary.
我不生气啊
I'm not mad.
真的？ 是啊…
Really? Oh yes
你遇到理查，简单吃点东西
So you bumped into Richard. You grabbed a "bite."
没啥大不了的
No big deal.
太好了
Great.
好，伦敦1分
Okay,London,1.
这将会是一场持久战
This is gonna be a real horserace.
怎么会这样
Oh,look what happened.
瞧瞧我自己
Check me out.
我在自家的厨房
I'm in my kitchen...
脱光光
...naked.
拿起一颗柳丁
I'm picking up an orange.
我脱光光
I'm naked.
点起蜡烛
I'm lighting the candles.
脱光光，要小心
Naked. And carefully.
天啊，瑞秋脱光光
Oh,my God! That's Rachel,naked!
不能看，我在看书
I can't look at that. I am looking at this.
好，鲜明的色彩、有力的笔触
Okay,vivid colors,expressive brush strokes.
她故意要我看就另当别论了
Unless she wants me to be looking at that.
她知道我在家
She knows I'm home.
她知道我看得到她
She knows I can see her.
她这是在玩什么把戏？
What kind of game is she playing?
也许今晚有人寂寞
I think maybe someone's lonely tonight.
盖勒博士，别胡思乱想 别傻了
Dr. Geller.Stop it. You're being silly.
真是这样吗？
Or am I?
讨厌
Darn it!
我可以进去吗？
May I come in?
想要的话就进来啊
Yeah,if you want to.
你要我进去吗？
Do you want me to?
当然？
Yeah,sure?
彼此彼此
So do l.
瑞秋，在一切还没开始之前
Okay,Rach,before anything happens...
有几个原则我想先说清楚
...I wanna lay down a couple of ground rules.
这只适用于今晚
This is just about tonight.
今晚过后，你是你，我是我
I won't go through with this if it'll raise the question of "us."
好吗？我希望这一切…
I just want this to be...
只是各取所需
...about what it is.
罗斯，什么各取所需？
And...what is that,Ross?
出自于兽欲的性爱
The physical act of love.
什么？你疯了不成？
What,are you crazy?
所以你刚才脱光光 不是在勾引我？
So you weren't trying to entice me just now with your nakedness?
天啊，你有看到？
Oh,God. You saw me?
你脱光光不是在勾引我
You weren't trying to entice me with your nakedness?
当然不是 你当真以为我想跟你上床？
You actually thought I wanted to have sex with you?
不是
No
不是…
No…
我很抱歉 可是你还把鞋踢掉了耶
Oh,wow. I'm sorry. But,Ross,you kicked off your shoes.
能不能忘了这件事？
-Can we just forget this ever happened?
当然可以，没问题 你说的对，抱歉
-Of course. You're right. I'm sorry.
谢谢
-Thank you. -Yes.
那我应该回去打包了 好
-I guess I'm gonna go pack. -Okay.
等等，还有一件事
Wait,one more thing.
还要解决我们的问题吗？
Do we still need to settle the question of "us"?
你们等等啊
Hey,you guys,wait!
等等我
You guys.
这地方比伦敦好多了吧
This place is much better than London.
有个打扮成埃及艳后的女士 给了我这张折价券
A lady dressed like Cleopatra gave me this.
99美分 就能吃到牛排龙虾晚餐
Ninety-nine cent steak and lobster dinner.
菲比，你又不吃肉
You don't eat animals.
只花99美分的话，我连你都吃
For ninety-nine cents I'd eat you.
我完全可以耗在这里 我要的东西应有尽有
I can totally settle down here.It's got everything I could ever want.
包括乔伊，你们看！
Including Joey! Look!
快点看！ 天啊
Look! Hey!Oh,my God.
乔伊！
Joey
你的保险套真不赖，伙计
Love your condoms,my man.
你们怎么在这里？ 不是要你们别来了？
Why are you here? I told you not to come.
你干嘛打扮成角斗士？
Why are you dressed as a gladiator?
因为我正在拍戏 我扮演角斗士
Because I'm shooting a scene right now. I play a gladiator.
你们等等
Hold on a second.
可以暂停一下吗？我朋友来了 我要休息一下
Can we cut?My friends are here. I'm gonna take a break.
你是在跟谁说话？
Who are you talking to?
导演啊，就是她
The director.Her.
好啦，我不是在拍角斗士 我在这里工作
All right,it's not a gladiator movie. I work here.
为什么？发生了什么事？
Why? What happened?
那部电影因为没钱而停拍
The movie shut down. Ran out of money.
我在这里工作等电影重新开拍 如果真有这一天的话
I'm working here till it starts up,if it ever does.
我真的很遗撼
-I'm so sorry. -Such a drag.
对不起，没跟你们说，抱歉
Sorry I didn't tell you. I'm sorry.
没关系… 互相隐瞒显然成了新的规矩
Apparently there's a new policy of not sharing.
我就知道你会纠结
-I knew you weren't okay with that.
你是角斗士耶
-So you're a gladiator!
他们怎么了？
What's going on?
莫妮卡跟理查吃了中饭
-Monica had lunch with Richard.
理查道森？ （演员）
-Dawson?
不是啦，要不然一定超酷的
But that would've been so cool!
是那个男朋友理查
Her boyfriend Richard.
那不意味什么 你怎么到现在还不相信我？
It meant nothing. After all this time,how can you not trust me?
你瞒着我跟大胡子帅哥吃午餐 要我怎么相信你？
When you go lunching with hunky men and don't tell me!
你说的对，对不起 我早该跟你说的
You're right. I'm sorry. I should've told you.
谢谢 这样才对嘛
Thanks.-There we go.
我爱拉斯维加斯
-Now I love Vegas.
我保证下次一定会跟你说
I promise you next time I absolutely will tell you.
下一次？
-"Next time"?
就差一点了
-So close.
不会有下次，你不能再跟他见面
There won't be a next time. You cannot see him again.
我不能跟他见面？ 你不能对我发号施令
I cannot see him? You can't tell me what to do.
有趣，刚才不就是了
That's funny,I think I just did.
你这种态度，我不想见到你 我无所谓
If you act like this,I won't be around you.-Fine.
好！纪念日快乐
-Fine，Happy anniversary!
你们别这样嘛 这显然是个大误会
Guys,please! Come on,come on.This is obviously a misunderstanding.
才不是误会 你在说什么…
No,it is not.
别看我，我只是在这里工作
Don't look at me. I just work here.
罗斯，我有点热，要脱毛衣
Okay,Ross? I'm a little warm,so I'm gonna be taking off my sweater.
我只是要你知道 这不是在勾引你兽欲的性爱
Now,I'm just letting you know...this is not an invitation to the physical act of love.
对，真是太爆笑了
Yep,that's hilarious.
抱歉，我不闹了…
I'm sorry. I'm done. I'm done.
昨晚对你其实也很尴尬
You know,last night was embarrassing for you too.
不尽然啦 你看过我裸体几百次了
No,not really. You've seen me naked hundreds of times.
但对我楼上的其他人是第一次 好吧
But it was a first for the rest of my building.
没错
That's true.
但我没有那么容易尴尬
But I just don't embarrass that easily.
什么？你完全尴尬得要死
What? You totally get embarrassed.
才没有 这是因为我比你更有安全感
No,I don't. Ross,I think I'm just a more secure person than you are.
是吗？ 是啊
-ls that so? -Yeah.
小姐，不管你有多想
Hey,lady!I don't care how much you want it,okay?
我绝不会和你去厕所做爱
I am not gonna have sex with you in the bathroom!
在古罗马时代 这不只是顶帽子而已
You know,in Roman times,this was more than just a hat.
是吗？ 当然…
-Really? -Yeah,sure,sure.
这可以用来刷地板
They would scrub the floors.
抹去鞋子上的泥巴
They'd use it to get the mud off their shoe.
有时候马的下部会脏 把这个戮进去就能…
Sometimes underneath the horse would get dirty.So they would stick it right
乔伊，真不敢相信 我的周年纪念日是这样过的
I can't believe this is how I'm spending my anniversary.
我带你去个好地方
I'll take you someplace nice.
今天有个人赏我一百美元小费
A guy tipped me $100.
他玩21点 才一小时就赢了五千美元
He was playing blackjack for an hour and he won $5000.
你相信吗？五千美元耶！
Can you believe that?
若我赢了五千美元 我就去加入健身房
If I won $5000,I'd join a gym.
把我的上半身练壮 再用棍子插理查的屁眼
Build up my upper body...and hit Richard from behind with a stick.
等等，我何不效法那个人？
Wait! Why don't I just do what that guy did?
把这一百元变成五千
I'll take this $100,turn it into $5000...
到时再连三翻 就有钱让电影重新开拍了
...and I'll turn that into enough to get my movie going!
祝你好运了
Good luck.
钱德，我不需要好运
I don't need luck.
我已经想透了 我懂了
I've thought this through.I see.
谢谢你 多谢
Thanks.
不敢相信，今晚真是糟透了
I can't believe this. This is like the worst night ever.
莫妮卡，你和钱德的关系 有了小小挫折
You had a minor setback in your relationship.
有啥大不了？不过是钱德罢了
Big deal. It's only Chandler.
我真的很遗撼
I am so sorry.
我们吵架的理由太蠢了 我根本不想跟理查再见面
This is crazy. Such a stupid argument....I don't wanna see Richard.
那就去挽回啊，去找钱德 他可能就待在你房间里
So go fix it.Find Chandler. He's probably in your room.
跟他说对不起，说你爱他
Tell him sorry and you love him.
菲比，你说的对，谢谢你 小意思
You're right,Phoebe.Thank you. -Sure.
好耶，拉斯维加斯  第一！
Yeah! Las Vegas! Number one!
这是谁掉的吗？
Anybody lose this?
下注吧
Coming out. Place your bet.
下好离手
Dice her out.
一赔二，不还本
Yellow 11. Pay the front line!
我正好要去厕所
So I'm on my way back to the bathroom.
好啦…继续走就是了
All right,all right. Just keep walking,all right?
罗斯，你干嘛… 先生，对不起，他太喜欢你了
Ross，What are you? I am sorry,sir.I think he just really likes you.
你知道那个老师吗？ 跟学生生孩子的那个？
You know that teacher who had a baby with her student?
搞什么…
What…
嗨 ，需要我效劳吗？
-Can I help you?
对，不好意思 你们有多的裤子吗？
-Yes.Do you have any extra pants?
我朋友出了点小状况
My friend seems to have had a little accident.
可以换一百元筹码吗？ 换一百元筹码
-Can I change $100? -Changing $100.
先生，祝您好运
-Good luck,sir. -Thanks.
全押了
That's right.
13点
-Thirteen.
再来
-Hit me!
要命！
Oh,man!
慢着！
Wait!
钱德，说了你一定不相信
You are not gonna believe this!
我找到我的双胞手了！
I have found my identical hand twin.
什么？
What?
我的双胞手啊！
My identical hand twin!
什么是双胞手？
What's an identical hand twin?
听起来像什么？ 有个人的手跟我一模一样
What does it sound like?It's a guy with my identical hands.
钱德，太不可思议了 发牌员的手跟我一模一样
It was incredible. The dealer's hands were exactly like mine.
就跟照镜子没两样
It was like looking at my hands in a mirror!
你确定不是在照镜子？
You sure you weren't looking at your hands in a mirror?
你不懂这件事的意义吗？
Don't you see what this means?
我大可忘了那部蠢电影
I can forget about that stupid movie.
我要变成百万富翁了！
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
怎么变？
-How?
我还没有完全想出来 不过保证很有赚头
-I don't have it all worked out yet.But it's gotta mean big money.
拜托，一模一样的手耶！
Come on,identical hands!
我得再问一次，怎么赚？
Again,I must go back to...how?
这里可是拉斯维加斯
This is Vegas,man.
大家就爱付钱看怪东西
People will pay to see freaky stuff!
好，你愿意付多少钱 看两次这只手？
How much would you pay to see this hand...twice?
乔伊，我说不太出个价钱
I can't really put a price on that.
你又不支持我了？
Are you un-supporting me again?
不…我百分之百支持你 只是我一时没回过神来
I support you 100%. I just didn't get it right away.
我现在懂了，双胞手！
Now I'm caught up.Identical hand twins.
这点子值上百万
It's a million-dollar idea!
我知道…
Right? I know. Okay. All right.
那是干嘛的？
What's that for?
照相存证，免得发牌员落跑
Well,I gotta document this before that dealer gets off his break.
了解了
I see
菲比
Phoebe
我找到我的双胞手了！
I found my identical hand twin!
你真幸运
Oh,you're so lucky!
莫妮卡呢？你们和好没？
So where's Monica? Did you guys make up?
没有
No
可是她刚才上来了啊
But she just came up here.
那是乔伊
That was Joey.
怪了，那她去了哪里？
I wonder where she is? It's so weird.
或许在跟理查说话吧
She's probably talking to Richard.
你有完没完？
Would you stop that?
你知道她和理查吃完中饭 回来后第一句话是什么吗？
You know what she said after her lunch with Richard?
她对他完全没感觉了 她爱的是你
She didn't feel anything for him. She loves you.
真的？ 对
-Really? -Yes.
而且她很难过
She feels terrible.
她真的很想跟你和好 你一定得找到她
She really wants to make up. You've gotta find her.
好
Okay
很好
Good.
我真应该开始戴帽子
I should really start wearing hats.
欢迎来到拉斯维加斯
Welcome to Las Vegas.
一路还愉快吗？ 对，谢谢，非常棒
-Did you enjoy your flight? -I did.Thank you very much. It was excellent.
希望您一路还愉快 太愉快了
-I hope you had a nice flight. -Oh,it was the best.
登记柜台应该在那里
I think the check-in is that way.
小孩子最喜欢我了
Kids love me.
菲比 你们来了！
Hi,you guys are here!
嗨 你去参加化妆舞会了？
What'd you do? Did you go to a costume party?
我来猜，你是扮潘乔维拉（墨西哥革命英雄）？ 你是鲍伯萨吉特（演员）
Let me guess. Pancho Villa.And you're Bob Saget.
潘乔维拉？ 是啊
Pancho Villa?-Yes
菲比，你在说什么啊？ 我不…
What are you talking about,Phoebe? I don't
天啊，你在我脸上画画？
Oh,my God! You drew on me?
谁叫你弄湿我裤子！
Hey,you wet my pants!
这是哪种派对啊？
What kind of party was this?
我打从下飞机就是这样子 你实在是太过份了
I've been walking around like this? You have so crossed a line.
瑞秋，等等，男厕在那里
Rach,wait. The men's room is that way.
怎么了？
What？
那个女的接我手玩，结果赢钱 这已经是第三次了
It's the third time she's won on a machine I was playing.
我赌她一定是那种人
I bet she's one of those people.
间谍？
Mole people?
不是啦，是潜伏人
What? No,a lurker.
潜伏人是什么？
What's that?
你玩赌博机，没有赢钱
When you're playing a machine and it hasn't paid out...
潜伏人等你放弃就来接手玩 然后…
...a lurker waits for you to give up and then
杀你灭口？
Kills you?
不是啦，他们半路杀进来 偷走你的运气
They swoop in and steal your jackpot.
你怎么会知道这种事
-How do you know about this?
我外婆以前就干这行
-My nana used to do it.
她就是用这收入 帮我付舞蹈…空手道的学费
That's how she paid for my dance Karate lessons.
舞蹈空手道？
Dance karate?
对，那是种美丽却致命的运动
Yes,it's a deadly...but beautiful sport.
我弄不掉
-lt won't come off.
什么？ 我弄不掉
-What? It won't come off.
天啊，瑞秋，你确定吗？
Oh,my God. Rach,are you sure?
不，其实我弄掉了 又自己再画回去
I took it off and then I drew it back on.
我真的很抱歉 我确定一定可以弄掉的
Rach,I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm sure we can get it off,okay?
把你的笔给我
-Just give me your pen.
干嘛？做什么用？
-Why? What are you gonna do?
我要让你万笔穿心
Well,I believe I'm going to stab you repeatedly.
别在这里 到处都有监视摄影机
Not here. There are cameras everywhere.
你们到了！
You made it!
乔伊
Joey
你朋友是谁？他真辣
Who's your friend? He's hot.
多谢夸奖
Thanks,man.
钱德跟我说过了 电影的事我很遗憾
Listen,I talked to Chandler. And I'm sorry about the movie.
不用抱歉，我已经不需要了
Don't be sorry.I don't need it anymore.
我找到我的双胞手
I found my identical hand twin.
你的什么？ 我的双胞手
Your what?My identical hand twin.
有个人的手掌跟我完全一样
The person whose hands are like mine.
你特别去找的？ 正好撞见的，这可是金矿
-Were you looking for this person? -Not even. This thing is a gold mine.
什么？靠那个赚不了钱的
What?That won't make you any money.
好，你这样想也无所谓
Well,fine.
到时我盖了手掌形的大厦 你们谁都休想来住
None of you will live with me in my hand-shaped mansion.
菲比，你例外，大拇指给你住
Except you. You can live in the thumb.
好吧，加油！
All right,baby,come on!
漂亮！挡都挡不住！
I am on fire!
莫妮卡，再见
See you later.
等等，钱德，你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
你看呢？我要回家
What's it look like? Going home.
等等，为什么？
Why?
钱德…你等等
Chandler…Wait
对不起，我只是下来玩一下
Sorry,I was just playing for one second.
我本来打算要跟你说 若你不让我跟理查再见面
If you don't want me to see Richard again,
我答应，他对我没有任何意义
I won't.He means nothing to me.
得了吧，我又不是瞎子
Oh,come on. I was there.
我知道他是你追求的真爱
I know he's the love of your life.
现在不是了
Not anymore.
真的？
Really?
真的
Really.
好了吗？
All right?
忘了什么要回家的事 我们来庆祝周年纪念日
Let's forget about going home and celebrate our anniversary.
袋子里是空的
Okay,this is empty.
我想要搞得很戏剧化 可是我又讨厌打包
I wanted to make a dramatic scene,but I hate packing.
另一个人呢？
Where's the other guy?
哪个人？
Which guy?
高高的，深色头发 手掌跟我一模一样，你看
Tall,dark hair,hand looks exactly like this?
我不知道什么手掌
I don't know about the hands,
不过在我之前的发牌员 刚去上厕所了
but he went to the restroom.
好
Okay
你好吗？
How you doing?
我很忙
-Very busy.
对！好
-Right. Okay.
你好，我有个问题
Yes,hello. I have a question.
我用你们的笔，画我朋友的脸
I used your pen to draw on my friend's face.
画了胡子
A beard and a mustache.
谢谢
Thank you.
不，她不这么想
No,she didn't think so.
对啊，那其实…
I know. It's like Anyway....
用化妆品盖不过去 我们试过所有方法都去不掉
Makeup didn't cover it,we've tried everything and nothing's worked.
这要怎么办？
What do we do?
对，是…
Yes…
好…多谢
Thank you.
对，这个墨水擦不掉
Yeah,it's not coming off.
什么？那他还说了什么？
What? What else did he say?
他说他觉得我很逗
He said he thought I was funny.
好，你听我说…
Okay,look. ...
我们下楼去好好玩 你就会忘记这回事了
Let's just go downstairs...we'll have some fun and you will forget all about it.
休想，罗斯，我顶着这个样子 绝对不出房门
There's no way I am leaving looking like this!
别这样啦，没有那么难看
Come on,Rach. It's not that bad.
罗斯，我变成人体涂鸦了！
Ross,I am a human doodle!
别因为一个白痴在你脸上乱画 而阻碍你玩乐的权利
Just because some idiot drew on your face doesn't mean you can't have fun.
而且又没人会看你
Besides,no one will even look at you.
这里可是拉斯维加斯，怪人一大堆
This is Vegas. Hello? There are tons of other freaks here.
这里有一大堆怪人，你不算
There are tons of freaks here. No other. No.
走啦，我发誓没人会注意到
Come on. No one will notice. I swear.
好啦，是有一些人指指点点
There was some staring and pointing.
我得喝点酒
I need a drink.
冰箱里的酒都太贵了
They really overcharge you for that stuff.
但是谁在乎呢？记在我的账上
But who cares,because it's all on me.
酒还真不少
That is one big drink.
要吃夏威夷果仁吗？
Macadamia nut?
这个果仁还真值钱
Wow! That's some pricey nut.
你真的很喜欢吃果仁吗
Really like those macadamia nuts?
不
Nope.
潜伏人，走开啦
Get out of here,you lurker!
滚啦
Go on,get!
菲比
Phoebe
你们和好了
You made up.
是啊，我没办法一直生他的气
I couldn't be mad at him for too long.
没有钱德的爱，她就不能活
She couldn't live without the "Chand love."
去开房间啦
Get a room.
我们有房间 我知道，快去用啊
-We have one. -I know，use it.
钱德，莫妮卡，再见
Bye,Chandler. Bye,Mon.
菲比…请至店内接电话 钱德和莫妮卡有事找
Phoebe,Phoebe. Please pick up a house phone.You have a call from Chandler and Mon.
喂？钱德、莫妮卡，喂？…
Hello,Chandler and Mon. Hello?
你这个死潜伏人
You dirty lurker!
打扰一下，你是那位老太太吧？
I'm sorry,you are the same old lady,right?
是的，死潜伏人！
Yeah. Dirty lurker!
可得好好照顾你的手
That's right. Take good care of those babies.
你说什么？ 我是乔伊
Excuse me?It's me. Joey.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
乔伊啊
Joey?
秀手的那个
Yeah,the hand guy.
我们要怎么处理双胞手的事？
So,what are we gonna do about this hand twin thing?
不用处理
Nothing.
你和我拥有上帝的赐礼
Look,you and I have been given a gift.
我们得要好好利用 好比手部模特儿或是变魔术
We have to do something with it. Like hand modeling. Or magic.
美国太空总署一定也想找我们聊聊
And you know NASA's gonna want to talk to us.
我得回去… 等等…
I have to get back to work.
我们可以有自己的表演秀
We can have our own show.
我们把手掌合在一起 大家一定超爱看的
We can clap our hands together. People will love it!
我还替我们写了一首主题曲
And I wrote a song for us.
这是你的手
This hand is your hand
这是我的手
This hand is my hand
等等，那是你的手才对
Oh,wait,that's your hand
不对，是我的手才对
No,wait,it's my hand
还是算了
-That's okay.
你还没听到和声啊
-But you haven't even heard the chorus!
天啊，我现在看起来 好像我姑婆莫瑞
Oh,my God.I look like my great-aunt Muriel.
其实我们用不着下楼
All right,you know what?We don't have to go downstairs.
房间里就可以是拉斯维加斯
We can bring Vegas up to us.
快，我们来玩21点
All right,come on.We'll play some blackjack.
让我们开始
Here we go.
13点 再加
-Thirteen. -Hit me.
Twenty-three.
我们的规矩23点最大
Which is what we play to at this casino!
你赢了10美元
You win 10 dollars!
我押了20美元 没错
-I bet 20. -Right.
帮我的小钱钱买双新鞋
A new pair of shoes for the Chan-Chan man!
好耶！
Yes
我这辈子还没看过有这么旺的
I've never seen a roll like this!
宝贝，你说对了
That's right,baby!
这次要押几号？
What do I want now?
好，8号…还是6号？
Eight?Six？
选一个！你只有这个任务！
- Pick a number! That is your only job.
8号… 8号
-Eight. -Eight.
如果你中了这一把 晚餐就请在场的各位吃牛排
If you get this,we buy everybody a steak dinner.
8号
Eight it is.
我们不会请他们吃牛排的对吧？ 是的
We're not buying steak dinners,are we?-No.
那就好
-Okay,good.
这次要押几号？
-What do I want now?
再押个难的8 什么？
-Try a hard eight.-What?
4加4 好
-Two fours. -Okay
8号
Eight!
千万要把握住她，你太幸运了
Don't you let her go. You're a lucky guy.
谢谢你，醉赌徒先生
Thank you,Mr. Drunken Gambler.
好，如果你中了这一把 我们就租下这里最大的套房
You get this and we get the biggest suite in the place.
等等…我说的我们是我和她
We get the biggest suite in the place.
好，这里最大的套房来啰
The biggest suite in the place!Come on!
好耶
Yes
我爱你 我都忘记我们在吵什么了
I love you! I can't remember why we fought.
因为我和理查吃中饭…
Because I had lunch with Rich
我也忘了！
Me neither!
这次要押几号？
-What now?
再押一次难的8
-Another hard eight.
难的8？简单8才对
Hard eight? Let's call it easy eight!
好，这样吧，如果这次再中…
I'll tell you what. You roll another hard eight...
我们今晚就在这里结婚
...and we get married here tonight.
快啊…
Go…
闭嘴！
Shut up!
好戏才正要上场！
It just got interesting!
你刚才说什么？
What did you say?
你再赢一次难的8 我们今晚就在这里结婚
You roll another hard eight,we get married tonight.
你是认真的？
You serious?
是啊，我爱你
Yes. I love you.
我不曾这样爱过一个人
I've never loved anybody as much as I love you.
我也不曾这样爱过一个人
好，如果再出8就是天意 我们赶今晚结婚
So if an eight comes up,we take it as a sign and we do it.
好不好？
What do you say?
好
Okay
来吧…
Come on
有一个是4，另一个呢？
That's a four.And where's the other one?
掉到桌子底下了
Under the table.
通通不许动！
Nobody move!
你找那边，我找这边 好！
You look that way,I look this way.
在这里…
Here it is,here it is.
4或者5
That could be 4 or 5.
你决定
It's your call.
那是4
It's a four.
我也这样觉得
I think so too.
好吧，又没赢到钱
Oh,well,lost again.
够了，我们去外面解决
That's it. You and me. Outside!
我可不想看到 你美丽的金发少了一撮
I wouldn't want you to lose a chunk of that pretty blond hair!
假装没事…
Be cool.
女士，你潜伏的日子结束了
Okay,your lurking days are over.
什么？
What?
从现在开始 我要抢先你一步
Everyone you lurk,I'll lurk first.
不管你找谁下手 我都会捷足先登
You move on,I'll be one step ahead of you...
一次都不放过
...every single time.
我每天都会紧紧跟着你…
And then I'll be on your ass every hour of every day...
直到星期一
...till Monday...
因为我那天要回家
...because that's when I go home.
你何时要回家？
When do you leave?
也是星期一
Also Monday.
几点？说不定能共乘计程车
What time? Maybe we can share a cab.
再加
Hit me.
Hit me
再加
我们得再去买牌
We need more cards.
对，还要再来点酒，你等等
Yeah. And we also need more drinks. Hold on a second.
好了
Okay
拉斯维加斯吗？
Hello,Vegas?
我们还需要酒 对了，再来点啤酒
We would like more alcohol.You know what else? We would like some more beers.
我竟然忘了拨号
Oh,I forgot to dial.
一定是送酒来了
That must be our alcohol and beers.
是乔伊！我爱乔伊
It's Joey! I love Joey!
我爱乔伊，乔伊跟鸭子住一起
Oh,I love Joey!Joey lives with a duck.
嗨
Hi
你们听我说，我需要帮助
Look,I need some help,okay?
谁去叫我那双胞手合作点
Someone has to convince my hand twin to cooperate.
我去
I'll do it.
不管你有什么需要 找我就对了
Whatever you need me to do,I'm your man.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
对，我很好，谢了
Yeah. Fine. Thanks.
瑞秋，你好吗？
Hey,Rach?How you doing?
宝贝，我很好，你呢？
I'm doing good,baby. How you doing?
罗斯，别再让她喝了
Don't let her drink anymore.
是那颗夏威夷果仁
Here's that macadamia nut.
不对，是别的东西
No,something else.
好吧，你现在要干嘛？
So,what do you wanna do now?
我要离开这房间
I wanna get out of the room.
我真想念楼下
I really miss downstairs.
我跟你说，要我离开这间房 只有一个方法
Okay,you know what? There is only one way I am leaving this hotel room.
嗨，我是罗斯
Well,hello!I'm Ross.
祝你好运
-Good luck to you.
抱歉，先生，你脸上有东西
-Sir,you've got a little something....
你好 你好
Hello.
你好
Hello
我赢了！…我终于赢了
I won!I won! I finally won!
是我赢才对，那是我的硬币
I won! That was my quarter!
好啦，还给你，滚吧
Take a hike,toots.
先生，不好意思
Excuse me,sir.
这位小姐用我的硬币玩 这是我赢的钱
This lady played my quarter. This is my money.
小姐，真的是这样吗？
Is that true,miss?
卖毒品给小孩
Sells drugs to kids.
什么？
What？
她卖毒品给小孩
She sells drugs to kids.
那是我的硬币
It was my quarter.
那硬币是她的吗？
Was it her quarter?
我们等吃晚餐再聊如何？
How about we talk about this over dinner?
好了，小姐，请你出去
-Okay,lady,you're out of here.
不！…你不能逮捕我
-No,you can't arrest me!
我才不要重回地狱！
I won't go back to that hellhole!
我只是要把你带出去而已
I'm just taking you outside.
那好吧
Oh okay
一定要凑齐旧的、新的、借的和蓝色的四样东西才能结婚（传统婚俗）
I need something old,something new,something borrowed and something blue.
好…
Okay
这是蓝色（纯洁）的，而且也是新（新人的美好生活）的
Here's something blue and new.
我们真有效率，我爱你
You are so efficient. I love you.
走吧 还不行…
-Let's go. -No,wait!
我们还需要旧（代代相传）的东西
We need something old.
好，我皮夹里有个保险套 我从12岁放到现在
I have a condom in my wallet that I've had since I was twelve.
有效
That'll work.
我想应该不能用了
I don't think so.
好，现在只剩借（财运和福气）来的东西
Now something borrowed.
那就把这毛衣拿走 这是偷窃耶
Here,just take this.That's stealing.
到时再还回来就是了 塞进你的裙子里
We'll bring it back. Put it under your dress.
好啦，先搞定一件事再说
Okay. One thing at a time.
你要玩吗？ 不 我没钱
-Are you gonna play? -No,I don't really have any money.
只是暂时没钱而已
Not yet,anyway.
你不玩就不能坐在这里
Can't sit here if you don't play.
嗨，我是瑞吉娜佛兰姬
My name is Regina Falangie.
我是生意人，这趟是来出差的
I'm a businesswoman in town on business.
你要我的名片吗？
Would you like to see my card?
我的名片夹到哪儿去了？
What did I do with my Filofax?
一定是忘在B会议室了
I must've left it in Conference Room B.
14点 再加
-Fourteen. -Hit me.
天啊，两位的手一模一样
Oh,my God.May I just say that you two gentlemen have the exact same hands?
一个模子刻出来的
They're identical.
我在商界做了这么久 从来没看过这种事
I've never seen that in the business world.
别再说了
Stop it.
佛兰姬女士，以局外人的身份 我能请教你一个问题吗？
Miss Falangie,may I ask you a question as an impartial person at this table?
请你别再说了
Please stop it.
你愿不愿意花大钱 去看手掌一模一样的两个人…
Wouldn't you pay good money to see identical hands...
这种娱乐性的演出？
...showcased in some type of an entertainment venue?
只要你愿意离开 我就把手砍下来送你！
If you leave now,I will chop off my hand and give it to you!
我不是才把你赶出去了吗？
Didn't I just throw you out?
不，你赶出去的是菲比 我是瑞吉娜佛兰姬 佛兰姬
No,you threw out Phoebe.I'm Regina Falangie. Falangie.
小姐，你别闹了
Come on,lady.
请你把他也带走
Please take him too.
我？别这样嘛
Me? Oh,come on,man.
走吧…
Come on,buddy.
你不能这样
Don't let him do this. Come on!
我是你的双胞手耶
I'm your hand twin!
嗨，登记结婚
Hello. One marriage,please.
对，我们要结婚
We want to get married.
有婚礼正在进行，先请坐
There's a service in progress. Have a seat.
好吧…
All right.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
那是结婚进行曲 听了有没有吓到？
The "Wedding March." Does that freak you out?
没有，因为那是毕业歌
No,it's the graduation song.
好，来吧
Okay，This is it.
我们要结婚了
We're gonna get married.
你确定你真的想结婚？
You sure you wanna do this?
嗨，罗斯太太
Hello,Mrs. Ross!
嗨，瑞秋先生
Well,hello,Mr. Rachel!
等等，好
Wait. Okay.